Lucy Kroll Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Client File, 1916-1998 (Box 1-736)
  - Lewin, John (Box 481)
    - House of Atreus (Box 483)
      - Austin Community College, Austin, Minn., 1976
      - Central High School, Duluth, Minn., 1967-1968
      - College of Marin, Kentfield, Calif., 1970
      - Memorial High School, Eau Claire, Wis., 1974
      - Minnesota Theatre Company
        - Contracts, 1967-1968
        - Correspondence, 1967-1970
        - Notes, 1968, undated
        - Photographs, 1967
        - Printed matter, 1967-1971
      - Miscellany
        - Correspondence and notes, 1967-1974
        - Performances, 1968-1984
      - Moline (Ill.) Public Schools, 1985
      - Roosevelt University, Chicago, Ill., 1986
      - Scott, Foresman, and Co., 1969
      - Script, 1969
      - Seattle University, Seattle, Wash., 1983
      - Southern Oregon State College, Ashford, Oreg., 1988-1989
      - Stephen F. Austin State University, Nacogdoches, Tex., 1987-1988
      - University of Arizona, Tucson, Ariz., 1989
      - University of Missouri, Kansas City, Mo., 1988
      - University of North Carolina, Asheville, N.C., 1971, 1990-1991
      - University of Saskatchewan, Saskatoon, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1981
    - Influence, 1979-1981
    - King Arthur (prologue), 1968-1970
    - King Oedipus
      - Contracts, 1970-1977, 1987
      - Correspondence
        - 1969-1970
        - 1971-1988, undated, (2 folders) (Box 484)
      - Financial records, 1971-1978
      - Notes, 1969-1980, undated
      - Printed matter, 1970-1979, undated
      - Script, 1970
    - A King of Infinite Space, 1972-1977, undated
    - The Last Temptation of Christ, 1960, 1968-1969, undated
    - Lorenzaccio
      - Contracts, 1971-1972
      - Correspondence, 1970-1972
      - Financial records, 1971-1972
      - Notes, 1970-1972 (Box 485)
      - Printed matter, 1972
      - Script, 1971
    - Lost Traveller, 1968, 1991-1993
    - Love Me, Love My Children, 1971
    - Lysistrata
      - Contracts, 1968-1974, 1985-1986
      - Correspondence, 1968-1986
      - Notes, 1968-1979, 1986
      - Photographs, 1968
      - Printed matter, 1968-1972, undated
      - Script, 1963
    - Miscellany
      - Biographical material and photograph, 1968-1977, 1992, undated
      - Correspondence
        - 1967-1975, (2 folders)
        - 1978-1983, 1995-1996, undated (Box 486)
      - Notes, 1967-1972, 1979-1983, undated
      - Printed matter, 1967-1968, 1974, undated
    - National Broadcasting Co., Prudential drama specials, 1968
    - Oedipus at Colonus For additional material see Containers 483-484, King Oedipus
      - Correspondence and notes, 1981, undated
      - Scripts, 1977-1979, (2 folders)
    - The Persians
      - The Crucible Theatre, Sheffield, England, 1971-1972
      - Miscellany
        - Correspondence, 1970-1973, undated
        - Notes and printed matter, 1970-1971
      - Phoenix Theatre, New York, N.Y.
        - Contracts, 1969
        - Correspondence, 1969-1970
        - Financial records, 1970
        - Notes, 1969-1970, undated
        - Printed matter, 1970
      - “Prologue,” undated
      - Scripts, 1969
    - Stages of Wholeness, undated For additional material see Container 487, Trophies of Defeat
    - The Surface of Water, 1968-1970 (Box 487)
    - Tango, 1967-1969, undated
    - The Tempest, “Masque,” 1971
    - Trophies of Defeat, 1983
    - Young Oedipus
      - Correspondence and notes, 1981-1982
      - Script, 1982
  - Lewis, Carol R., 1965
  - Lewis, Edna See Containers 323-325, Huganir, Elma
  - Lewis, Jenifer, 1984, undated
  - Libarle, Marc
    - Contracts, 1969-1970
    - Correspondence, 1970-1973
    - Notes, 1970-1972, undated
    - Printed matter, 1970-1971, undated
    - Typescripts, 1970, undated
  - Lide, Miller, 1964
  - Lieberman, Herbert, 1991-1993, undated
  - Lind, Robert (“Bob”), 1987-1991, undated
  - Lindfors, Viveca, 1950-1952, undated
  - Linney, Romulus (Box 488)
    - The Adventures of St. Peter, 1974-1975, undated
    - “The American Parade,” “The 34th Star,” 1973-1974
    - Appalachia Sounding
      - Miscellany, 1975-1976
      - Script, undated
    - Childe Byron, 1979-1981
    - Children's Television Workshop, “Feeling Good,” 1974-1975
    - The Death of King Phillip, 1966, 1974
    - Democracy
      - Correspondence, 1968-1977, undated, (2 folders)
      - Milwaukee Repertory Theatre, Milwaukee, Wis., 1975-1976
      - Notes, 1968-1976, undated
      - Printed matter, 1969-1970, undated
      - Script, undated (Box 489)
      - Temple University, Philadelphia, Pa., 1976
      - Virginia Museum Theatre, Richmond, Va.
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1973-1974, undated
        - Notes and printed matter, 1972-1974, undated
        - Photographs, 1974
    - Hadrian VII, 1967-1968, undated
    - Holy Ghosts
      - Contracts, 1973-1975, undated
      - Correspondence, 1971-1976, undated
      - Notes, 1971-1976, undated
      - Printed matter, 1971-1976, 1987, undated
      - Scripts, 1974-1976, undated, (3 folders)
    - Just Folks (Box 490)
      - Miscellany, 1974-1976, undated
      - Script, 1975
    - The Lonely Way (alternate title Der Einsame Weg ), 1967
    - The Love Suicide at Schofield Barracks
      - Contracts, 1970-1971, undated
      - Correspondence, 1970-1976, undated, (2 folders)
      - German language rights, 1971-1973, undated
      - Notes, 1971-1976, undated, (6 folders) (Box 491)
      - Printed matter, 1971-1972, undated
      - Scripts, 1971, (2 folders)
    - Man's Estate: Five Plays (Box 492)
      - Miscellany, 1966-1975, undated
      - Script, 1969, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1964-1977, undated
      - Notes, 1973-1975, undated
      - Printed matter, 1962-1974, 1980-1981, 1987-1989, undated
    - The Sorrows of Frederick
      - Birmingham Repertory Theatre, Birmingham, England
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1969-1973, undated
        - Notes, 1969-1972, undated
        - Printed matter, 1969-1972, undated
      - Burgtheater, Vienna, Austria
        - Contracts and correspondence
          - 1968-1969, (2 folders)
          - 1970-1973, undated (Box 493)
        - Notes, 1968-1970, undated
        - Printed matter, 1968-1970, undated
        - Royalty statements, 1968-1973, undated
      - Center Theatre Group, Los Angeles, Calif.
        - Contracts, 1966-1968
        - Correspondence, 1966-1968, undated, (3 folders)
        - Financial records, 1966-1971
        - Notes
          - 1966-1967, (3 folders)
          - 1968, undated (Box 494)
        - Printed matter, 1966-1968, undated See also Oversize
        - Royalty statements, 1967-1972
        - Scripts, 1966-1967, (2 folders)
      - Düsseldorfer Schauspielhaus, Düsseldorf, Germany
        - Correspondence, 1968-1969, undated
        - Notes, 1968-1969, undated
        - Photographs, 1969
        - Printed matter, 1969-1970, undated
      - East Carolina Playhouse, Greenville, N.C., 1968-1969
      - Film offers
        - Correspondence, 1966-1976
        - Notes, 1966-1976, undated
      - Foreign rights and productions, 1966-1976, undated (Box 495)
      - Frostburg State College, Frostburg, Md., 1972
      - Harcourt, Brace, and Jovanovich
        - Miscellany, 1966-1970, undated
        - Royalty statements, 1968-1972, 1981-1989
      - Miscellany
        - Correspondence, 1967-1980, 1991, undated, (2 folders)
        - Notes, 1967-1976, undated, (2 folders)
        - Photographs, undated
      - Oberlin College, Oberlin, Ohio, 1968-1969
      - Playhouse Theatre Company, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1971-1972
      - Robert Whitehead Productions
        - Correspondence, 1968-1970, undated, (2 folders)
        - Notes
          - 1968-1969
          - 1970-1971, undated (Box 496)
      - St. Clement's Church, New York, N.Y.
        - Correspondence, 1975-1976
        - Notes, 1975-1976, undated
        - Printed matter, 1975-1976
      - Scripts, 1966, 1974-1976, (4 folders)
      - Virginia Museum Theatre, Richmond, Va., 1971-1972
    - Slowly, by Thy Hand Unfurled
      - Correspondence, 1965-1973, 1993, undated
      - Foreign rights
        - 1964-1965
        - 1966-1976, undated (Box 497)
      - Notes and printed matter, 1965-1972, undated
      - Royalty statements, 1966-1975
    - 2, 1992, undated
  - Lipsky, Eleazar
    - The Baby, 1951-1953
    - The Criminal Mind, 1948
    - Father's Day, 1948
    - The Guilty Ones, 1948-1949
    - Idaho, 1949-1950
    - Indictment
      - Contracts, 1958
      - Correspondence, 1956-1962, undated
      - Financial records, 1958
      - Notes, 1956-1959, undated, (3 folders)
      - Printed matter, 1959, undated
    - Johnny O'Hara's Life, 1949
    - Kiss of Death, 1947-1950, 1956-1958, undated
    - Lincoln McKeever (Box 498)
      - Contracts, 1953-1956, undated
      - Correspondence, 1953-1960, undated, (4 folders)
      - Financial records, 1953-1959
      - Outline for television, 1954
      - Notes, 1953-1960, undated
      - Printed matter, 1953-1955, undated
    - The Man Who Rocked the Boat, 1956
    - Miscellaneous
      - Biographical material, undated
      - Contracts, 1946-1959, undated
      - Correspondence
        - 1947-1956, (2 folders)
        - 1957-1962, 1968, undated (Box 499)
      - Notes, 1947-1955, undated
      - Photograph, undated
      - Printed matter, 1949-1953, undated
    - Murder One
      - Correspondence, 1947-1962, (3 folders)
      - Notes, 1950-1959, undated
    - The New York City Story, 1957
    - People Against O'Hara, 1949-1966, undated
    - The Quality of Mercy, 1952-1963, undated
    - The Scientists
      - Book
        - Contracts, 1951-1961, undated
        - Correspondence
          - 1955-1957
          - 1958-1966, undated, (5 folders) (Box 500)
        - Financial records, 1958-1966
        - Foreign rights
          - England
            - Longmans, Green, and Co., 1958-1967, undated
            - Other publishers, 1956-1959, undated
          - Other countries, 1958-1960, undated
        - Notes, 1955-1966, undated, (2 folders)
        - Printed matter, 1959-1960, undated (Box 501)
      - Play
        - Correspondence, 1959-1961
        - Notes and printed matter, 1959-1961, undated
        - Script, 1961
    - Stabbing in the Streets, 1951-1956
    - Three Nickels Dropped, 1955-1956
    - Tiger in the Night (formerly titled Country Boy ), 1954-1963, undated
    - Woman in Flight (formerly titled The Fourth Degree )
      - Contracts, 1952-1953, undated
      - Correspondence, 1947-1960, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes, 1953-1956, undated
      - Printed matter, 1952-1953, undated
      - Scripts, 1952, undated For additional material see Container 317, Hinton, Jane, and Container 499, Murder One (Box 502)
    - When Hannah Var Eight Yar Old, 1947-1953
  - Liss, Joseph, 1955, 1968-1975, 1985, undated
  - Little, Joan See Containers 328-329, Jones, Isaac, and Container 536, Paul, Jerry
  - Littner, Ner, 1978, undated
  - Litvin, Martin, 1986-1987
  - Locke, Katherine
    - Contracts, 1949
    - Correspondence, 1945-1952
    - Miscellany, 1950, undated
    - Printed matter, 1937-1942, 1950, undated
  - Locke, Samuel
    - The Drum
      - Correspondence, 1961-1962
      - Miscellany, undated
      - Script, undated
    - “The Lady and the Lion,” 1954-1956
    - “The Maze,” 1954-1958, undated
    - Miscellany
      - Contract, 1954
      - Correspondence, 1954-1962, undated
      - Notes, 1954-1962
    - Strange Bedfellows
      - Contract, 1962
      - Correspondence, 1962-1964
      - Miscellany, 1962-1964, undated
    - The Vamp, 1954-1955 See also Container 453, Latouche, John (Box 503)
    - The Woman with Red Hair
      - Contracts, 1948-1967, (3 folders)
      - Correspondence
        - 1943-1963 See also Oversize, (4 folders)
        - 1964-1968, (2 folders) (Box 504)
      - Financial records, 1949-1968
      - Notes, 1948-1967, undated, (2 folders)
      - Printed matter, 1949-1968
      - Scripts, 1964-1967, undated, (3 folders)
  - Lockwood, Sara
    - Contracts, 1946-1947
    - Correspondence
      - 1946
      - 1947-1952, undated, (3 folders) (Box 505)
    - Miscellany, 1946-1947, undated
    - Royalty statements, 1948-1951
  - Lodge, Lilly
    - Contracts, 1960-1962
    - Correspondence, 1957-1963, undated
    - Notes, 1957-1964, undated
    - Printed matter, 1958-1962, undated
  - Loftis, Norman J., 1973-1977, undated
  - Lorant, Stefan, 1990-1993, undated
  - Lord, Jack, 1955-1960, undated
  - Loren, Richard, 1977-1981, undated See also Container 188, Garcia, Jerry
  - Lortz, Richard
    - The Juniper Tree
      - Contracts, 1967-1968
      - Correspondence, 1967-1969
      - Notes, 1968-1969, undated
      - Script, undated
    - Leonardo
      - Correspondence, 1967
      - Script, undated (Box 506)
    - Miscellany, 1958, 1967-1968, undated
    - The Others
      - Contracts, 1966-1968, undated
      - Correspondence, 1966-1969, undated, (7 folders)
      - Financial records, 1967
      - Notes, 1967-1969, undated
      - Printed matter, 1966-1967
      - Script, undated
    - Poor Child (Box 507)
      - Contracts, 1955-1969
      - Correspondence, 1967-1969
      - Miscellany, 1967, undated
      - Script, undated
    - A Summer in Spain, 1960, 1967-1969, undated
    - Three Sons
      - Correspondence, 1968-1971
      - Miscellany, 1968-1970, undated
      - Script, undated
  - Losey, Joseph, 1951-1952, undated
  - Love, Nancy, 1980, undated
  - Lubin, Natalie, 1968-1969
  - Lundy, Deborah, 1979
  - Lunt, Alfred, 1971-1974
  - Lyons, Augusta Wallace, 1956, 1964, undated
  - Maas, Audrey, 1963-1965, undated
  - Maas, Peter, 1964-1965, undated
  - Mabley, Edward H., 1980, undated
  - MacArthur, Charles
    - Cock-a-Doodle Daisy (formerly titled Glory Be! )
      - Correspondence, 1955-1960
      - Miscellany, 1954-1960, undated
    - Fun to Be Free, 1961-1962, undated (Box 508)
    - Jumbo, 1934, 1945-1946, 1961
    - Lulu Belle, 1959-1960
    - Miscellany, 1954-1964, undated
    - The Senator Was Indiscreet, 1958
    - War Bugs, 1963, 1969-1970
  - MacArthur, James
    - Contracts, 1958-1960
    - Correspondence, 1959-1972, (2 folders)
    - Notes, 1958-1960, 1972, undated, (2 folders)
    - Printed matter, 1955-1962, 1970, undated
  - MacColl, Ray Oliver
    - Henry Ossian Flipper, 1975
    - Miscellany, 1973-1977, undated
  - MacDonald, Angus, 1969-1970, undated
  - Macdonald, Brian
    - Contracts, 1987-1992, undated
    - Correspondence, 1983-1992, (2 folders) (Box 509)
    - Notes, 1983-1989, (7 folders)
    - Photograph, undated
    - Printed matter, 1982-1992, undated, (4 folders) (Box 510)
  - MacDonald, Robert David
    - Contracts, 1977-1979, undated
    - Correspondence, 1978-1980, (3 folders)
    - Notes, 1978-1980
    - Printed matter, 1976-1979, undated
    - Script, undated
  - MacDonald, Roberta, 1961-1965, undated (Box 511)
  - MacIntyre, Thomas, 1972-1973, undated
  - Macosko, Greg, 1976, undated
  - MacPherson, Margaret, 1949-1955, undated For additional material see Containers 323-324, Huganir, Elma, Ceremony of Innocence
  - Macy, Marianne, 1990
  - Magdalany, Philip, 1968-1970, undated
  - Magnum Photos, Inc., 1988
  - Mailer, Norman
    - Contracts, 1948-1950
    - Correspondence, 1948-1951, (2 folders)
    - Notes, 1948-1949
    - Printed matter, 1948-1951
  - Mally, Anita, 1980, 1986
  - Maltz, Albert, 1946-1948, 1966-1971
  - Mancini, Al, 1962-1964, undated
  - Mandel, George, 1952-1957, undated See also Container 308, Heller, Joseph, and Container 313, Heyman, Kenneth
  - Mann, Abby, and Bernard Drew, 1951-1952, undated (Box 512)
  - Marchand, Philip, 1973-1978, undated
  - Marengo, Francesca (“Peggy”), and Alison G. Smith
    - Contracts, 1990-1991
    - Correspondence, 1988-1991
    - Notes, 1991, undated
    - Printed matter, 1991
    - Typescript, 1991
  - Margolin, Janet
    - “Alcoa Presents,” “The Hands of Donafrio,” 1962
    - “Ben Casey,” 1962-1963
    - Daughter of Silence, 1961-1962, undated
    - David and Lisa
      - Contracts, 1962
      - Correspondence, 1962-1963, undated
      - Financial records, 1962-1965
      - Notes, 1962-1963, undated
      - Photographs, 1962
      - Printed matter, 1962-1963, undated See also Oversize
      - Script, 1962
    - The Greatest Story Ever Told (Box 513)
      - Contracts, 1962
      - Correspondence, 1962-1965
      - Financial records, 1962-1963
      - Notes, 1962-1963, undated
      - Printed matter, 1962-1963
    - Miscellany
      - Contracts, 1961-1963
      - Correspondence, 1961-1965, (3 folders)
      - Financial records, 1961-1965
      - Notes, 1961-1965, undated, (3 folders)
      - Photographs, circa 1962-1963
      - Printed matter, 1961-1965, undated
    - Morituri, 1964
    - Nevada Smith, 1965
    - “United States Steel Hour,” “Two Black Kings,” 1962
  - Marker, Laury See Container 660, Spencer, Nelsie
  - Markinson, Brian, 1990, undated
  - Marsh, Linda
    - Contracts, 1962-1964
    - Correspondence, 1962-1964, undated (Box 514)
    - Notes, 1962-1964
    - Printed matter, 1962-1964
  - Marshall, William, 1964, undated
  - Martin, George Victor
    - Contracts, 1947-1949
    - Correspondence, 1947-1949, undated, (3 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1945-1953, undated
    - Royalty statements, 1948-1952
  - Martin, Nancy Fales, 1964-1967
  - Marvin, Blanche
    - Chekhov's Two Sisters
      - Contract, 1981
      - Correspondence, 1980-1982
      - Film outline, 1992
      - Notes, 1981, undated
      - Scripts, 1980, undated
    - London Theatre Reviews, 1989-1993 (Box 515)
    - Miscellany
      - Correspondence, 1980-1995
      - Notes, 1965-1968, circa 1980-1981
      - Printed matter, 1959-1964, 1980-1981, undated
    - Thief of London
      - Contract, 1991
      - Correspondence, 1991-1994
      - Notes, 1991-1992, undated
      - Scripts
        - Version III, 1984
        - Version IV, 1991
  - Mattern, Kitty, 1959-1964, undated
  - Matthau, Walter
    - Contracts, 1952-1957
    - Correspondence
      - 1952-1954, (3 folders)
      - 1955-1957, 1993-1994 (Box 516)
    - Financial records, 1952-1957
    - Notes, 1952-1957, undated, (2 folders)
    - Printed matter, 1952-1957, undated
  - Matthews, Elizabeth, 1971-1972, undated
  - Matthews, John F.
    - Contracts, 1948-1950, 1960
    - Correspondence, 1948-1951, 1959-1965, (2 folders)
    - Notes, 1948-1950, 1959-1962, undated
    - Printed matter, 1949, 1959, undated
  - Mattos, Edward, 1967, undated
  - May, Monica
    - Contracts, 1960-1964
    - Correspondence, 1960-1965
    - Notes, 1962-1963, undated (Box 517)
    - Printed matter, 1961-1964
  - McAssey, Michael, 1986-1987, undated
  - McAulay, Sara, 1979-1981, undated
  - McCutchen, Heather L., 1990
  - McDonough, Ann, 1975, undated
  - McElroy, Njoki, 1989-1990
  - McGill, Earle L., 1946-1948, undated
  - McGrath, Donald, 1975-1979, undated
  - McGrath, Kristina, 1979-1980
  - McGrath, Russell, 1967-1972, undated
  - McHugh, Edna, 1974
  - McInerny, Paul M., 1984-1985
  - McKinsey, Beverlee
    - Barefoot in the Park, 1964-1966
    - The Cliffdwellers, 1965-1966
    - Commercials and voice-overs, 1964-1965, undated
    - “The Defenders,” 1965
    - Dutchman, 1964-1965
    - “The Make-Believe Clubhouse,” 1960, undated (Box 518)
    - Miscellany
      - Contracts, 1963-1964
      - Correspondence, 1964-1966
      - Notes, 1964-1966, undated
    - “The Nurses,” “The Attacker,” 1965
    - “On the Seaway,” 1965
    - “The San Francisco Series,” 1965
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf? 1964
  - McLanathan, Richard, 1987-1988
  - McQuade, John, 1955-1959, undated
  - McQuillan, Colin M., 1981-1982
  - Meara, Anne, 1957-1962, undated See also Container 676, Stiller, Jerry
  - Megyeri, Steven A., 1985
  - Meiser, Edith, 1981
  - Melchiorre, Sherry, 1988
  - Menen, Aubrey, 1950-1954, undated
  - Menninger, Karl
    - Correspondence, 1977-1982
    - Miscellany, 1977-1982, undated
    - Typescripts, 1978-1982
  - Merrill, Claire Birsh
    - “Helen Hayes: Portrait of an American Actress”
      - Miscellany, 1970-1972, undated
      - Script, 1970 (Box 519)
    - “Who's Afraid of Opera?” 1971-1977, undated
  - Mesco, Richard H., 1990, undated
  - Meyer, Janice C., 1984-1985, undated
  - Mikanovich, Sergio, 1965
  - Miller, Andrea, 1961
  - Miller, Anne, 1963
  - Miller, Catherine Lanham, 1987
  - Miller, Jason, 1971-1972, undated
  - Miller, Victor B., 1974, undated
  - Mills, Elaine P., 1984-1985, undated
  - Minahan, John
    - A Clock Without Hands, 1960-1961
    - Goodbye, Darkness, 1966-1972, undated
    - Jeremy
      - Contracts, 1973
      - Correspondence, 1973-1978
      - Notes, 1974-1977
      - Printed matter, 1973
      - Typescript, 1973
    - Miscellany (Box 520)
      - Correspondence, 1962-1977, undated
      - Notes, 1962-1977, undated
      - Printed matter, 1966, 1971, 1986
    - Morales, Ricardo, project, 1977 See also Container 525, Morales Family
    - The Passing Strange
      - Contracts, 1965-1972, 1979-1980
      - Correspondence, 1963-1980, (4 folders)
      - Notes, 1963-1980, undated
      - Printed matter, 1965, 1971-1973
      - Royalty statements, 1966-1969
    - A Sudden Silence
      - Contracts, 1962-1964
      - Correspondence
        - 1961-1962
        - 1963-1970, undated, (2 folders) (Box 521)
      - Notes, 1961-1970, undated
      - Printed matter, 1962-1963, 1970
      - Royalty statements, 1962-1972
    - Victories, 1973-1974, undated
  - Mintz, Steven L., 1979-1981, undated
  - Mintzer, Joanna Luria, 1979-1980, undated
  - Misch, Paul, 1982
  - Moiseiwitsch, Tanya, 1978
  - Mokae, Zakes
    - Contracts, 1970-1971
    - Correspondence, 1970-1976, undated
    - Notes, 1970-1976, undated
    - Photographs, undated
    - Printed matter, 1970-1972, 1982-1985, 1995
    - Script, undated
  - Monet, Dorothy (Box 522)
    - Cold Soup, 1987-1989, undated
    - Cyprienne
      - Contracts, 1955
      - Correspondence, 1954-1955
      - Financial records, 1955
      - Notes, 1955, undated
      - Printed matter, 1955
    - McComber
      - Correspondence, 1986-1989, (3 folders)
      - Miscellany, undated
      - Notes
        - 1986
        - 1987-1988, undated, (2 folders) (Box 523)
      - Printed matter, 1986-1988, undated
      - Scripts, 1986-1987, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany
      - Contracts, 1982
      - Correspondence, 1955-1956, 1987-1988, undated
      - Notes, 1955-1956, 1986-1989, undated
      - Printed matter, 1959, 1971, 1986-1987, undated
    - The Wrastling and the Fall, 1952-1954, undated
  - Monroe, Steve, 1991-1993, undated
  - Montgomery, Ed
    - Miscellany, 1955-1958, undated
    - Typescript, 1956 (Box 524)
  - Moor, Paul
    - Contract, 1980
    - Correspondence, 1993
    - Notes, 1993
    - Printed matter, 1993, undated
    - Typescripts, 1993, undated
  - Moore, Alma and Roy, 1991
  - Moore, Dick, 1975, 1982-1983, undated
  - Moore, Douglas For additional material see Containers 454-456, Latouche, John, and Containers 525-526, Moross, Jerome
    - Carry Nation, 1958, 1965-1968, undated
    - Gallantry, 1958
    - Miscellany, 1956-1966, undated
    - The Wings of the Dove, 1960-1962
  - Morales family See also Container 520, Minahan, John (Box 525)
    - Contracts, 1976
    - Correspondence, 1976-1980, (2 folders)
    - Court records, 1976
    - Notes, 1976-1978, undated
    - Photographs, 1975, undated
    - Printed matter, 1977
  - Moross, Jerome
    - Ballet Ballads See Containers 457-458, Latouche, John
    - The Big Country, 1958
    - Blood Wedding, 1949-1953
    - Chu Chen, 1964-1965
    - Close-Up, 1947-1948
    - The Day after Tomorrow, 1955
    - Gentlemen, Be Seated (Box 526)
      - Correspondence, 1958-1963, (2 folders)
      - Music, 1966
      - Notes, 1958-1963
      - Printed matter, 1964
      - Script, undated
    - The Golden Apple See Containers 458-461, Latouche, John, and Jerome Moross
    - The Last Judgment, 1953